{
    "id": "93ecd42c8212477584d3182e02e9b2c4",
    "title": "Agreements And Disagreements",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "James doesn’t like cricket. …………………….",
            "description": "Negative additions to negative remarks are made with nor/neither + auxiliary + subject.",
            "answers": [
                "Nor I do",
                "Nor do I",
                "So do I"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a5f68edf44e4457fb060c3b16874d22d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was late for the meeting. ………………………….",
            "description": "Affirmative additions to affirmative remarks are made with so + auxiliary + subject.",
            "answers": [
                "So was he",
                "So he was",
                "Nor was he"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "50d2f8579212436bb779dd5a6a3e15e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She passed the test and …………………………. did I.",
            "description": "Affirmative additions to affirmative remarks are made with so + auxiliary + subject.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "nor",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "db9a6d6a09fb40a5b75f299e2e1d6a7b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have finished my job and …………………………. has he.",
            "description": "Affirmative additions to affirmative remarks are made with so + auxiliary + subject.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "nor",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "806d59fc1d174f868b694296abb72fbe"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie didn’t arrive. ……………………….. did Mary.",
            "description": "Negative additions to negative remarks are made with nor/neither + auxiliary + subject.",
            "answers": [
                "So",
                "Neither",
                "Nor"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "11e435d8581d4a7f94e8937d1b44cf99"
        },
        {
            "question": "He didn’t buy it. ……………………………. did I.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Nor",
                "So",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "252bfe05ff3640a2b9fa28eabc5cac11"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can play chess ………………………… he can’t.",
            "description": "Negative additions to affirmative remarks are made with but + subject + auxiliary + n’t.",
            "answers": [
                "nor",
                "and",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "025406914a0048148013ebb892d829e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She knows how to swim, but ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I don't",
                "don't I",
                "I know not"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ba024b98fc81428e96d7b67b263fc076"
        },
        {
            "question": "My husband doesn’t watch movies …………………………… I do.",
            "description": "Negative additions to affirmative remarks are made with but + subject + auxiliary + n’t.",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "and",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf33547a6bbe4a8f8281a7f67c75a559"
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t complain. Neither …………………………… her husband.",
            "description": "The same auxiliary is used in both statements.",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "does",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd1141286ad14d56bde8f772db929ef5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know you don’t like me. I don’t like you ……………………….",
            "description": "Don't either means the same as neither. ",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "adf0b436531646928af34c31b2a05ac0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is married. ……………………………… her sisters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "So are",
                "So is",
                "Nor are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5c54b1e4a87e4b6cb61ed51bdc16e55f"
        }
    ]
}